His city. His rules. No prisoners.
Sinners and Saints is a action, crime, thriller
film directed by William Kaufman.
In lawless storm ravaged New Orleans, eleaguered Detective Sean Riley is trying to
cope with the death of his young son and the abandonment of his wife.
Facing a probable suspension from the department, Riley is teamed with a young homicide Detective, Will Ganz,
to help solve a series of brutal murders that have plunged the city into a major gang war.
The two quickly realize there is something far more sinister
going on than either could have ever imagined.
Detective Sean Riley, played by Johnny Strong.
Detective Will Ganz, played by Kevin Phillips.
Raymond Crowe, played by Costas Mandylor.
Colin, played by Sean Patrick Flanery.
Captain Trahan, played by Tom Berenger.
Detective Dave Besson, played by Kim Coates.
Sinners and Saints is a 2010 action-thriller film directed by William Kaufman; co-written by Kaufman and Jay Moses; and starring
Johnny Strong, Kevin Phillips, Costas Mandylor, Sean Patrick Flanery, Bas Rutten, Method Man, Kim Coates and Tom Berenger.
The film is set in the dark underbelly of New Orleans.
It was released in North America on DVD and Blu-ray on January 10, 2012.
The film explores themes of gang war, shootout, semiautomatic pistol.
The tone is dark and intense.